Guide to the George B. Post Architectural Records and Drawings Collection PR 53
© 2011 New-York Historical Society
- Wisconsin State Capitol - Madison, WI
  - Grounds - f.s.d. of bronze bubble fountain; graphite on trace (damaged), 1914-05-12 (Box 399)
  - North Wing - suggestion for model #318 (metal), eagle/wreath; graphite on trace, 1915-08-05 (Box 399)
  - North Wing - suggestion for model #319 (metal registers); graphite on trace, 1915-08-05 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - counter & cases at south entrance to restaurant; graphite on trace (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - octagonal case at center of restaurant; graphite on trace, 1916-12-21 (Box 399)
  - Grounds - revised layout of NE approach; graphite on trace, 1916-03-13 (Box 399)
  - Bronze door & frame for fire alarm boxes; graphite on trace, 1916-04-28 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - 1st floor rotunda plan; graphite on trace (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - ground floor rotunda plan; graphite on trace (Box 399)
  - South Wing - center table for senate; graphite on trace, 1912-10-22 (Box 399)
  - Senate seating plan, scheme A; graphite on trace, 1912-06-08 (Box 399)
  - South Wing - design for revolving bookcase for senate; graphite on trace, 1912-09-20 (Box 399)
  - Bronze door & frame for fire alarm boxes; graphite on trace, 1916-04-28 (Box 399)
  - Capitol Park - elevation & section of pedestal & vase in front of seats in approach; graphite on trace, 1916-05-21 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - spacing of letters on galleries at second floor level; graphite on trace, 1914-05-14 (Box 399)
  - Grounds - plan showing sidewalks, trees & lighting; graphite on trace, 1914-05-27 (Box 399)
  - South Wing - reading desk to sit on clerk's desk of senate, 1913-01-15 (Box 399)
  - North Wing - suggestion for model #317 (metal) ornamental; graphite on trace, 1915-08-05 (Box 399)
  - North Wing - suggestion for model #315 (metal) ornamental; graphite on trace, 1915-08-05 (Box 399)
  - North Wing - suggestion for model #316 (metal) ornamental; graphite on trace, 1915-08-05 (Box 399)
  - North Wing - suggestion for model #309, ornamental; graphite on trace (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - ground floor, course 5 NW marble layout; graphite on trace (Box 399)
  - Elevator fronts: electric push buttons; graphite on trace (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - SW corner pavilion: change in communicating doors; graphite on trace (Box 399)
  - Light standards in stair hall; graphite on trace, 1913-12-19 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - special locking device for triple hung sash in dome; graphite on trace, 1913-12-31 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - part of sheets 2026 & 2028, attic & ring course plans; graphite on trace, 1912-09-19 (Box 399)
  - South Wing - center table for senate; graphite on trace, 1912-10-02 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - NW corner pavilion: shoe shining stand in barber shop; graphite on trace, 1917-02-28 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - spacing of letters on galleries; graphite on trace (3 sheets) (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - 1st floor column & pilaster bases; graphite on trace, 1913-10-22 (Box 399)
  - Brass cuspidor (spittoon); ink on linen (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - ground floor plan; graphite on trace, 1914-02-26 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - locating mosaic panels in pendentive; graphite on trace, 1914-04-18 (Box 399)
  - West Wing - temporary senate rooms 105-106; graphite on trace (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - suggestion for indication of wings; graphite on trace, 1913-12-09 (Box 399)
  - Lettering for "audience room"; graphite on trace (Box 399)
  - Lettering for "hearing room"; graphite on trace (Box 399)
  - Detail of lamp standard; graphite on trace, 1912-10-14 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - change in windows, circular staircases of dome; graphite on trace, 1914-04-25 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - change in additional beams & ground floor; graphite on trace, 1914-01-28 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - registers in stone walls; ink on trace, 1913-09-03 (Box 399)
  - North Wing - bottom rail window sash; graphite on trace, 1915-05-03 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - granite capstone forming base for bronze statue; graphite on trace, 1913-01-17 (Box 399)
  - Detail of marble molding from drawing #2043; graphite on trace, 1912-09-06 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - 1st floor plan, revision of "tinos" pilasters; graphite on trace, 1913-01-08 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - rosettes in panels above large windows of dome; graphite on trace, 1914-02-26 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - basement floor, change in entrances to restaurant; graphite on trace, 1912-09-30 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - method of anchoring statue on lantern of dome; ink on trace, 1914-02-16 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - SE & NW pavilions: rearrangement of fixtures with additional wash basins; graphite on trace, 1914-02-16 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion/Grounds - change revising straight seats, approaches; graphite on trace, 1914-11-10 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - possible position of mail chutes in corner pavilions; graphite on trace, 1917-07-13 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - basement, N & S corridors to restaurant: change in meeting rails of doors; graphite on trace, 1914-04-23 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - change in swing of doors to serving room, basement; ink on trace, 1913-05-17 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - SE pavilion, plan of toilet room; graphite on trace, 1914-02-16 (Box 399)
  - Capitol Park - detail plan of walks & driveways to corner pavilions & wings; graphite on trace (damaged), 1912-09-30 (Box OS-7)
  - Central Portion - cornice of east & west ends of main stair hall, 1st floor; graphite on trace (damaged, folded, poor condition) (Box OS-7)
  - Diagrammatic plan of building; graphite on manila, 1906-06-12 (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - ground floor rotunda plan; aniline print on paper (damaged) (Box 399)
  - Central Portion - 1st floor rotunda plan; aniline print on paper (damaged) (Box 399)
- Arthur Turnbull House - Gladstone, NJ
  - Detail of skylight; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Dining room & porch fireplaces; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Mantel in NW bedroom; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Mantel in NE bedroom; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Attic windows; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Mantel in SW bedroom; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Attic stairs; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Detail of cornice & base; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Living room: north elevation; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Details of library; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Details of dining room; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Living room: east elevation (Box 335)
  - Living room: south elevation; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Living room: west elevation; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Details of dining room; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Revised plan of framing for stair hall; graphite on trace, 1914-09-26 (Box 335)
  - 2nd floor: wood pilasters, plaster transom, window stool & apron; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Details of entrance hall; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Stair hall toward pantry; graphite on trace, 1914-09-28 (Box 335)
  - Stair hall toward entrance hall; graphite on trace, 1914-09-28 (Box 335)
  - Stair hall toward east wall; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Details of stair hall; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Plans of stairs to attic (4); graphite on trace, 4 sheets (Box 335)
  - Detail of pantry & kitchen dressers; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Living room: east elevation; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Living room: south elevation; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Plan of tile entrance & stair halls; graphite on trace, 1915-03-13 (Box 335)
  - Main stairs: carved baluster; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Living room: north elevation; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Plan of plaster ceiling in living room; graphite on trace, 1916-02-05 (Box 335)
  - Living room: west elevation; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Sketch of stairs; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Living room: north elevation; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Copper leader head; graphite on trace, 1914-10-28 (Box 335)
  - Details of attic stairs; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Stair hall toward east wall; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Closet in dressing room; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Sketch showing handrail; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Details of main stairs; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Mantel in library; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Dining room toward stair hall; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Dining room toward library; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Dining room: elevation of west wall; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Dining room: elevation of south wall; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Main stairs: change in handrail; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Stair hall: panelling on east wall; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - 2nd floor: typical door & window trim; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Details of cornices for bedrooms & 2nd sty stair hall; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Stair hall toward dining room; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Library: elevation of fireplace; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Library: elevation of wall opposite fireplace; graphite on trace, 1914-10-06 (Box 335)
  - Library: elevations toward porch; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Detail of brick stoop; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Mantel in NE chamber; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Mantel in NW chamber; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Mantel in SW chamber; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Hall toward dining room; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - North elevation of living room; graphite on trace (damaged, 2 pieces) (Box 335)
  - Hall: elevation of east wall (Box 335)
  - Living room: east elevation, schemes II & V; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Plaster ceiling in living room; graphite on trace, 1916-04-25 (Box 335)
  - Living room: north & west elevations, scheme V; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Living room: south elevation, scheme V; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Living room: south elevation, scheme I; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Living room: north & west elevations; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Living room: east elevation; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - 2nd floor framing at main stairs; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Sketch of stairs; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Limestone facings for bedrooms & dining room; graphite on trace (damaged) (Box 335)
  - Heads over 2nd fl windows for blinds; ink on linen, 1915-01-26 (Box 335)
  - Copper leader boxes; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Plaster ornament over stair window; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Sketch of mantel [?]; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Unidentified interior elevations; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Details of dining room & main entrance doors; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Attic stairs; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Registers in dining room; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Hall toward library; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - Hall toward living room; graphite on trace (Box 335)
  - 54 E 74th St. NYC Turnbull residence - plaster ceiling in dining room; graphite on trace, 1923-09-27 (Box 335)
  - Detail of mullioned window in kitchen; graphite on trace (Box OS-11)
  - Measured drawing of dining room; graphite on trace (Box OS-11)
  - Fireplaces in library & dining room; graphite on trace, 1914-06-08 (Box OS-11)
  - Sections thro' old & new wings of house; graphite on trace (Box OS-11)
  - Belt course at 2nd floor level; graphite on trace (Box OS-11)
  - Chimney in old building; graphite on trace, 1914-06-09 (Box OS-11)
  - Rear service stairs; graphite on trace, 1914-06-11 (Box OS-11)
  - Detail of north chimney fireplaces & structural steel; graphite on trace (Box OS-11)
  - French casement windows; graphite on trace (damaged), 1914-06-02 (Box OS-11)
  - Detail of brick & cement porch floor; graphite on trace, 1915-03-29 (Box OS-11)
  - Detail of library mantel; graphite on trace (Box OS-11)
  - Profiles of woodwork for living room; graphite on trace, 1916-04-21 (Box OS-11)
  - Living room: center panel over mantel; graphite on trace, 1916-06-08 (Box OS-11)
  - Suggestions for the use of espagnolette bolts (Russell & Erwin Mfg. Co.); blueprint on paper (damaged) (Box OS-10)
  - Stair hall: panelling on east wall; blueprint on paper (Box 335)
  - Stair hall: section thro' stairs; blueprint on paper (Box 335)
  - Stair hall toward entrance hall; blueprint on paper, 1914-09-28 (Box 335)
  - Stair hall toward pantry; blueprint on paper, 1914-09-28 (Box 335)
  - Living room: north & west elevations; blueprint on paper (2 copies) (Box 335)
  - Hall toward library; blueprint on paper (Box 335)
  - Dining room: elevation of west wall; blueprint on paper (Box 335)
  - Living room: south elevation; blueprint on paper (Box 335)
  - Living room: east elevation; blueprint on paper (Box 335)
  - Living room: south elevation; blueprint on paper (Box 335)
  - Conduit runs for 1st floor bells; blueprint on paper (Box 335)
  - Conduit runs for 2nd floor bell & light work; blueprint on paper (Box 335)
  - Mantel in living room, 1st fl.; blueprint on paper, 1916-06-03 (Box 335)
  - Dining room toward stair hall; blueprint on paper (Box 335)
  - Cornices for bedrooms & 2nd story stair hall; blueprint on paper (Box 335)
  - Details for 1st & 2nd story porches; graphite on trace (poor condition) (Box OS-10)
  - Living room details, casement windows; graphite on trace, 1916-05-24 (Box OS-10)
  - Living room: detail over mantel; graphite on trace, 1916-06-07 (Box OS-10)
  - Detail of main entrance; graphite on trace (Box OS-10)
  - Details of cornice, dormer windows & window at main stair; graphite on trace (Box OS-11)
  - Living room: large casement windows; graphite on trace, 1916-05-24 (Box OS-11)
  - Detail of 2nd floor casement & double hung windows; graphite on trace (poor condition) (Box OS-11)
  - Living room: detail of mantel; graphite on trace, 1916-05-25 (Box OS-11)
  - 1st floor: casement & double hung windows; graphite on trace, 1914-06-02 (Box OS-11)
  - Detail of dining room mantel; graphite on trace (Box OS-11)